?Are you ready, kids-
？你们准​​备好了吗，孩子们——
.KIDS: Aye, aye, Captain
.KIDS：是的，是的，队长
.I can't hear you-
.我听不到你说话-
.KIDS: Aye, aye, Captain
.KIDS：是的，是的，队长
Oh, [SINGING] who lives in-
?a pineapple under the sea
哦，[唱歌]谁住在-
？海底的菠萝
.KIDS: Spongebob Squarepants
.KIDS：海绵宝宝
CAPTAIN: [SINGING] Absorbent
.and yellow and porous is he
队长：[唱歌]吸收剂
.黄色且多孔的是他
.KIDS: Spongebob Squarepants
.KIDS：海绵宝宝
CAPTAIN: [SINGING] If nautical
.nonsense be something you wish
船长：[唱歌]如果是航海的话
.nonsense 是你想要的东西
.KIDS: Spongebob Squarepants
.KIDS：海绵宝宝
CAPTAIN: [SINGING] Then drop on
.the deck and flop like a fish
船长：[唱歌]然后下来
.像鱼一样翻牌并翻牌
.KIDS: Spongebob Squarepants
.KIDS：海绵宝宝
?CAPTAIN: [SINGING] Ready
？队长：[唱歌]准备好
.Spongebob Squarepants
.海绵宝宝
!Ha
！哈
[WAVE SOUNDS]
[波浪声]
[SEAGULLS]
[海鸥]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐播放]
[BUBBLE SOUNDS]
[泡泡声]
?Patrick-
？帕特里克-
?Patrick
？帕特里克
?Oh, Patrick
？哦，帕特里克
Are you ready to
?go jelly fishing
你准备好了吗
？去钓果冻
[MUSIC]
[音乐]
.Oh, boy, am I-
.哦，孩子，我是-
.Here's your net-
.这是你的网络-
.Well, come on, Patrick
.好吧，来吧，帕特里克
The jellyfish don't
.catch them themselves
水母没有
.亲自抓住他们
First I have to put-
.away my secret box
首先我必须放-
.拿走我的秘密盒子
?Secret box-
?秘密盒子-
You never told me
.about your secret box
你从来没有告诉过我
.关于你的秘密盒子
.Hey, hands off peepin' Bob-
.嘿，放开偷看鲍勃的手-
.This here is my secret box
.这是我的秘密盒子
Besides, if I showed
,you what was inside
此外，如果我展示
，你里面是什么
.it wouldn't be a secret anymore
.这不再是秘密了
.Duh
.呃
Doh, Spongebob, if only you
,could see inside my secret box
噢，海绵宝宝，如果只有你就好了
,可以看到我的秘密盒子里面
.it would change your life
.它会改变你的生活
.It's OK, Patrick-
.没关系，帕特里克-
.I know all about secrets
.我知道所有的秘密
?You do-
？你做-
.I've got a gazillion secrets-
.我有无数的秘密-
?Like what-
？就像什么-
Well, it's no secret that-
the best thing about a secret
嗯，这不是什么秘密——
关于秘密最好的事情
is secretly telling someone your
secret thereby secretly adding
正在偷偷地告诉某人你的
秘密从而秘密添加
another secret to their
--secret collection of secrets
他们的另一个秘密
——秘密的秘密收集
.secretly
。偷偷
You want to hear
?one of my secrets
你想听
？我的秘密之一
?Do I-
？我——
.Uh, let's see-
.呃，让我们看看-
Did you know you're
?my best friend
你知道你是
？我最好的朋友
.No way-
。决不-
.Let's hear another one
.让我们听听另一首
OK, uh, secretly I'm-
.a little bit naive
好吧，呃，私下里我是——
.有点天真
!Wow-
！哇-
I'll never look at you the
.same way again, Spongebob
我永远不会看着你
.同样的方式，海绵宝宝
.Gosh
.天啊
.Tell me some more secrets
.告诉我更多秘密
.OK-
。好的-
I love my job at
.the Krusty Krab
我热爱我的工作
.蟹堡王
.I sleep with my shoes on
.我穿着鞋子睡觉
I like jelly on both
.sides of my toast
我都喜欢果冻
.我的吐司的两面
I've got an overdue
.library book
我有逾期的
.图书馆书籍
I think jelly fishing
and bubble blowing
我认为果冻钓鱼
和吹泡泡
are the-- I've never
.been late for work
是——我从来没有
.上班迟到了
I've said the word
.fancy in conversation
我说过这句话
. 对话中的花哨
I like to dance to loading
.zone announcements
我喜欢随着加载而跳舞
.区公告
I still don't have
.my driver's licence
我还没有
.我的驾驶执照
.I'm a little on the short side
.我有点短
And I'm wearing three pairs
.of underwear right now
而且我穿了三双
.现在的内衣
.Gasp-
。喘气-
.I never would have guessed
.我从来没想到
Now will you show me what's-
?inside your secret box
现在你能告诉我什么是-
?在你的秘密盒子里
.No, Spongebob-
.不，海绵宝宝-
.It's for me to know
.这是让我知道的
.And for you to never find out
.并且让你永远不会发现
You may be an open
.book, Spongebob
你可能是一个开放的
.书，海绵宝宝
But I'm a bit more
.complicated than that
但我有点多
.比那复杂
The inner machinations
.of my mind are an enigma
内心的阴谋
.我的心里是个谜
[MUSIC]
[音乐]
?Oh, yeah-
？哦，是的-
Well, I got plenty
.of secret stuff too
嗯，我有很多
.还有秘密的东西
.Uh, I've got my secret socks on
.呃，我穿上了秘密袜子
.And my secret Gary's bowl
.还有我的秘密加里的碗
My secret TV and my
.secret TV channel
我的秘密电视和我的
.秘密电视频道
[BEEP]
[嘟]
What do you think of
?that that, Patrick
你觉得怎么样
？那个，帕特里克
?Patrick
？帕特里克
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐播放]
Maybe if you saw-
,what was inside
也许如果你看到-
,里面是什么
you'd know why it
.has to be secret
你会知道为什么
.必须保密
Inside this very box
is the most secrety
在这个盒子里
是最隐秘的
.secret in all of secretdom
.一切秘密中的秘密
.And I am its sole witness
.而我是它唯一的见证人
.It's a heavy burden, Spongebob
.这是一个沉重的负担，海绵宝宝
But nobody must know
.the mystery of the box
但没人知道
.盒子之谜
!Nobody
！没人
.Not even Squidward's house
.连章鱼哥的家都没有
.It's a full-time job
.这是一份全职工作
.I'm constantly on the alert
.我时刻保持警惕
You never know when
--someone's going to, oh
你永远不知道什么时候
——有人会，哦
[BOING]
[轰鸣]
!Spongebob
！海绵宝宝
?What do you think you're doing
？你认为你在做什么
.That's my secret box
.那是我的秘密盒子
.Now, hand it over
.现在，把它交给
But Patrick, I must-
.know the secret
但是帕特里克，我必须——
.知道秘密
,For the last time-
.Spongebob, no
,最后一次——
.海绵宝宝，不
.Come on, just a peek-
.来吧，只是看一眼-
!Never-
！绝不-
!Oh-
！哦-
.So it's come to this-
.所以事情就这样了——
And to think we joined the
.best friends forever club
想想我们加入了
.永远最好的朋友俱乐部
[MUSIC]
[音乐]
Listen up, Spongebob-
,secret stealer" Pants"
听着，海绵宝宝——
、秘密窃取者“裤子”
if you ever come near
,my secret box again
如果你走近
，我的秘密盒子又来了
.we won't be friends anymore
.我们不再是朋友了
But we are supposed-
.to be friends forever
但我们假设——
.永远做朋友
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐播放]
.I feel so filthy-
.我感觉好肮脏-
I have soiled our
.friendship garden
我弄脏了我们的
.友谊花园
.I just couldn't help myself
.我只是无法控制自己
.I know it's your secret
.我知道这是你的秘密
.I promise to respect that
.我保证尊重这一点
Oh, please forgive
.me, Patrick, please
哦，请原谅
.我，帕特里克，请
Well, I guess it's-
.not all your fault
嗯，我猜是——
.不全是你的错
After all, this is a
.pretty great secret
毕竟，这是一个
.相当大的秘密
I mean, how could you resist the
greatest secret ever-- the most
我的意思是，你怎么能抗拒
有史以来最大的秘密——最
amazing, mysterious, powerful
?secret in all of Bikini Bottom
惊人的、神秘的、强大的
?比基尼泳裤的全部秘密
?So what do you say, buddy-
？那么你说什么，伙计-
?Friends
？朋友们
.Friends-
。朋友们-
[BUBBLE SOUND]
[泡泡声]
What could be in that box that-
?Patrick doesn't want me to see
那个盒子里可能有什么——
？帕特里克不想让我看到
Maybe it's the world's
.only albino jellyfish
也许这就是世界上
.只有白化水母
Or maybe Patrick's a
.master jewel thief
或者也许帕特里克是
.珠宝大盗
.And it's full of diamonds
.而且里面都是钻石
Or maybe Patrick's
a deranged maniac
或者也许是帕特里克的
一个疯狂的疯子
who keeps his victim's
.severed heads in a box
谁保留受害者的
.盒子里的断头
Or even worse, maybe it's
an embarrassing snapshot
或者更糟糕的是，也许是
尴尬的快照
.of me from a Christmas party
.来自圣诞晚会的我
[SCREAM]
[尖叫]
I've got to find out
.what's in that secret box
我必须找出答案
.那个秘密盒子里有什么
.I'm not going to rest till I do
.我不会休息直到我这样做
.That's it
。就是这样
How do you look
?into a secret box
你看起来怎么样
？放进秘密盒子里
.Secretly, of course
.当然是秘密的
I'll just take the box while
Patrick's sleeping, look
我就拿一下盒子
帕特里克正在睡觉，看
inside, and before Patrick
,even has time to notice
在里面，在帕特里克之前
,甚至有时间去注意
.I'll slide it back
.我会把它滑回来
.Patrick won't know
.帕特里克不会知道
And I'll have my
.own little secret
我会有我的
.自己的小秘密
?Good idea, eh, Gary
？好主意，呃，加里
.Mmm, no-
.嗯，不-
?Oh, what do you know-
？哦，你知道什么-
.You're a snail
.你是一只蜗牛
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐播放]
[SNORING]
[打鼾]
.Cecil dressing-
.塞西尔敷料-
[SNORING]
[打鼾]
?Who is
?谁是
.Oh, oh
.哦哦
[CRACKING SOUND]
[破裂声]
.Secret
。秘密
.I've got to be more quiet-
.我必须更安静-
.I don't want wake Patrick up
.我不想叫醒帕特里克
[SLIDING SOUND]
[滑动声]
[CRASH]
[碰撞]
.Oh, oh
.哦哦
.SNORING] Doh]
.打鼾]Doh]
.Oooh, da
.噢，达
.Mmm
.嗯
!CRASH] Doh]
！崩溃] Doh]
?Who's that
？那是谁
.Oh, eh, oh
.哦，呃，哦
!BREAKING GLASS] Hey]
！打破玻璃]嘿]
?Lilla, hoozum
？莉拉，胡祖姆
[SNORING]
[打鼾]
[BOMB SOUND]
[炸弹声]
[BOOM]
[繁荣]
.Mmm, water
.嗯，水
[SNORING] [CRASH]
[打鼾] [崩溃]
[MACHINE GUN SOUND]
[机枪声]
[ELEPHANT SOUND]
[大象的声音]
[RACE CAR SOUND] [CRASH]
[赛车声音][碰撞]
.SNORING] Good old secret box]
.SNORING]好旧的秘密盒子]
.Let's see what's inside
.让我们看看里面有什么
.Nighty night boxy
.Nighty night 四四方方
[SNORING] [BOING]
[鼾声] [嗡嗡声]
[CRASH]
[碰撞]
[ANIMAL SOUNDS]
[动物的声音]
[CRASH] [BREAKING GLASS]
[DIVE BOMB SOUND] [BOOM]
[碰撞][玻璃破碎]
[俯冲炸弹声] [轰隆]
[SNORING]
[打鼾]
Gee, Patrick sure-
.is a heavy sleeper
哎呀，帕特里克当然——
.睡得很沉
!Oh-
！哦-
?Who said that
？谁说的
?Who's there
?谁在那儿
.Uh-
.呃-
.It's the clam burglar-
.这是蛤贼-
.And he's stealing my secret box
.他正在偷我的秘密盒子
Hand over the goods
.secret box bandit
移交货物
.秘密盒子强盗
And prepare for
the most unpleasant
并做好准备
最不愉快的
!pillow fight of your life
!你一生的枕头大战
!Wait, wait, wait, Patrick-
！等一下，等一下，帕特里克——
!Stop
！停止
.It's me
。这就是我
.Spongebob
.海绵宝宝
.Nice try, burglar-
.不错的尝试，窃贼-
.But Spongebob's my best friend
.但是海绵宝宝是我最好的朋友
.And he'd never steal from me
.他永远不会偷我的东西
.No, really, Patrick-
.不，真的，帕特里克-
.Look
。看
.Oh-
。哦-
SINGING] It's the]--
,best friends forever
唱歌]这是]--
,永远最好的朋友
.best friends forever, ring
.永远最好的朋友，响铃
!Our friendship ring-
!我们的友谊戒指-
.It is you
.是你
?SOBBING) How could you do this)
？抽泣）你怎么能这样做）
If it makes you-
,feel any better
如果它让你——
,感觉好多了
.I haven't looked inside
.我还没看过里面
.That's it Spongebob-
.这就是海绵宝宝-
.You have crossed the line
.你已经越界了
As of right now, this
!friendship is over
截至目前，这
！友谊结束了
?Really-
？真的-
Nah, you can look inside-
.if you really want to
不，你可以看看里面——
.如果你真的想
.OK-
。好的-
Oh, this is one of the most
.exciting moments of my life
哦，这是最
.我生命中激动人心的时刻
.Well, here it goes
.好吧，就这样
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐播放]
?Huh
？哈
?Well-
？出色地-
?Didn't I tell ya
？我不是告诉过你了吗
?Isn't it great
？这不是很棒吗
.It's just a string-
.这只是一个字符串-
!A secret string-
!秘密字符串-
.Boy, when you're right-
.男孩，当你是对的时候-
.You're right
。你说得对
That's some secret
.box you got there
这是一些秘密
.box 你到了那里
Yeah, thanks for
.showing me that
是的，谢谢
.向我展示
.Well, good night, Patrick
.好吧，晚安，帕特里克
.See you tomorrow
。明天见
.Good night, Spongebob-
.晚安，海绵宝宝-
.I should have known-
.我应该知道-
It was just a piece
.of string all along
本来只是一块而已
.of 字符串一直
.Wait till I tell Gary
.等我告诉加里
LAUGHING] Good]
thing you didn't pull
笑]好]
你没有拉的东西
the secret string opening
the secret compartment
秘密字符串开头
秘密隔间
.of my secret box
.我的秘密盒子
Really, what an
embarrassing snapshot
真的，什么是
尴尬的快照
of Spongebob at that
.Christmas party
海绵宝宝的那个
.圣诞晚会
LAUGHS] Merry]
!Christmas, Spongebob
笑]快乐]
！圣诞节，海绵宝宝
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐播放]
[BUBBLE SOUNDS]
[泡泡声]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐播放]
[DOORBELL]
[门铃]
Yeah, uh, we're with the-
.pet hospital down the street
是的，呃，我们和-
.街上的宠物医院
And I understand you have a
.dying animal on the premises
我知道你有一个
.场内垂死的动物
[PHONE RINGING]
[电话铃声]
?Hello-
？你好-
You've reached the house
.of unrecognised talent
你已经到家了
.未被认可的人才
--Please start after the
--请在以下时间后开始
[HORN SOUND]
[喇叭声]
Sounds as though-
you've got a dying
听起来好像——
你快要死了
animal to attend
?to, eh, old chum
动物参加
？致，呃，老朋友
Squilliam Fancyson-
?from band class
斯奎利亚姆·芬西森-
?来自乐队课
I hear you're playing-
--the cash register now
听说你在玩——
——现在的收银机
.Sometimes-
。有时-
?Uh, how's the unibrow
？呃，一字眉怎么样
.It's big and valuable-
.它又大又有价值-
I'm the leader of a
.big, fancy band now
我是一个人的领导者
.现在是大而华丽的乐队
And we're supposed to play
.the Bubble Bowl next week
我们应该玩
.下周的泡泡碗
?The Bubba Bowl , the Bubba-
？布巴碗，布巴-
?The Bubba
？布巴
.That's right-
。这是正确的-
I'm living your
.dream, Squidward
我过着你的生活
.梦，章鱼哥
The problem is I'm busy
.next week and can't make it
问题是我很忙
.下周但没能成行
So I was hoping you and your
.band could cover for us
所以我希望你和你的
.band 可以为我们提供掩护
--Oh, I-- I-- I-- I, uh-
--哦，我--我--我--我，呃-
.I knew it-
。我就知道-
.You don't even have a band
.你甚至没有乐队
Well, I'll just let you get back
.to the service industry now
好吧，我会让你回来
.现在转向服务业
!Hold it-
！坚持住——
It just so happens that
.I don't sell fast food
恰巧的是
.我不卖快餐
.I do have a band
.我有一个乐队
And we're gonna play
.that Bubble Bowl
我们要玩
.那个泡泡碗
?How do you like that, fancy boy
？你觉得怎么样，漂亮的男孩
.Good luck next Tuesday-
.祝下周二好运-
I hope the audience
.brings lots of ibuprofen
希望观众
.带来大量布洛芬
I've got to drum up-
.a marching band fast
我得鼓起勇气——
.一支快速的行进乐队
.Drum, ha, ha, band humour
.鼓，哈哈哈，乐队幽默
Looking to add fulfilment"-
".to your dull, dull life
希望增加满足感”-
“.对你平淡无奇的生活
Then become part of"-
the greatest musical
然后成为“的一部分”-
最伟大的音乐剧
sensation ever to
".hit Bikini Bottom
曾经的感觉
“.打比基尼泳裤
And be forever"-
adored by thousands
并永远”——
受到成千上万人的崇拜
".of people you don't know
“.你不认识的人
Not to mention"-
".free refreshments
更不用说”——
“.免费茶点
Practise begins"-
".tonight-- 8:30 sharp
练习开始”——
“.今晚——8点30分整
Stupid music rental-
.clerk made me late
愚蠢的音乐出租-
.店员让我迟到了
That trilobite didn't know
.an oboe from an elbow
那只三叶虫不知道
.肘部的双簧管
,Hmm, elbow, hmm
.more band humour
，嗯，肘部，嗯
.更多乐队幽默
[CROWD CHATTER]
[人群议论]
.Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah-
. 巴拉，巴拉，巴拉，巴拉，巴拉-
.People, people, settle down-
.人们，人们，安定下来-
OK now, how many
of you have played
现在好，有多少
你们中的一些人玩过
?musical instruments before
?之前的乐器
Do instruments-
?of torture count
做乐器-
？酷刑计数
.No-
。不-
?Is mayonnaise an instrument-
?蛋黄酱是一种工具吗-
No, Patrick, mayonnaise-
.is not an instrument
不，帕特里克，蛋黄酱——
.不是乐器
Horseradish is not
.an instrument either
辣根不是
.一个乐器
.That's fine
。没关系
.No one has any experience
.没有人有任何经验
Fortunately, I have enough
--talent for all of you
幸好我有足够的
——给大家的才华
.ha, ha-- all of you
.哈哈——你们所有人
.Yeah
。是的
?When do we get the free food-
？我们什么时候能得到免费食物-
.OK, try to to repeat after me-
.好吧，试着跟我重复一遍-
[CLARINET SOUND]
.Brass section-- go
[单簧管声音]
.铜管部分--走
[HORNS PLAYING]
[喇叭演奏]
.Now the wind
.现在风
[HORNS PLAYING]
[喇叭演奏]
And the drums
还有鼓
[SPLAT]
[啪]
[RICHOCHET]
[理查切特]
SARCASTIC) Too bad)
.that didn't kill me
讽刺）太糟糕了）
.那并没有杀死我
Let's just try
.stepping in rhythm
让我们尝试一下
.踏着节奏
Now, I want everyone to stand
.in straight rows of five
现在，我希望大家起立
.直排五个
Is this the part-
?where we start kicking
这是这个部分吗——
？我们从哪里开始踢
No, Spongebob, that's-
".A Chorus Line"
不，海绵宝宝，那是——
“.合唱线”
?Kicking-
？踢-
.Oh, I want to do some kicking
.哦，我想做一些踢
!Oh
！哦
--Why you-
——为什么是你——
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
[战斗声音]
!Oh-
！哦-
!Ho, ho ho
！嗬嗬嗬
Whoever is the owner
,of the white sedan
谁是主人
,白色轿车的
.you left your lights on
.你没关灯
[HORN PLAYING]
[喇叭演奏]
.ANNOUNCER: Day two
.播音员：第二天
[WHISTLE]
[哨]
.OK, that's perfect, everybody-
.好吧，这很完美，大家-
.Bubble Bowl here we come
.泡泡碗我们来了
Flag twirlers, really
.spin those thing
确实是国旗旋转者
.旋转那些东西
.OK, turn
.好的，转
.Flag twirlers, let's go
.旗帜旋转者，我们走吧
.I want to see some spinning
.我想看一些旋转
!Flag twirlers, let's move
！旗帜飘扬者，让我们行动起来
!Come on, move
！来吧，动起来
[PLANE SOUNDS]
[飞机声音]
[CRASH]
[碰撞]
[TAPS PLAYING]
[点击播放]
.ANNOUNCER: Day three
.播音员：第三天
How's that harmonica-
?solo coming, Plankton
那口琴怎么样-
？独奏来了，浮游生物
.It's tremendous-
.这真是太棒了-
?You want to see
？你想看
[PANTING]
[气喘吁吁]
[HARMONICA SOUND]
[口琴声音]
[PANTING]
[气喘吁吁]
[HARMONICA SOUND]
[口琴声音]
[PANTING SOUND]
[喘气声]
[HARMONICA SOUND]
[口琴声音]
[PANTING SOUND]
[喘气声]
[SPLAT]
[啪]
,Oh-
，哦-
.ANNOUNCER: Day four
.播音员：第四天
Well, this is our last night-
.together before the show
好吧，这是我们的最后一晚——
.演出前一起
And I know that you haven't
.improved since we began
我知道你还没有
.自我们开始以来有所改善
.But I have a theory
.但我有一个理论
People talk loud when they
?want to act smart, right
人们大声说话时
？想要表现得聪明，对吧
!Correct-
！正确的-
,So if we we play loud-
.people might think we're good
，所以如果我们大声演奏-
.人们可能认为我们很好
?Everybody ready
?大家准备好
,And the one, and the two
.and a one, two, three, four
,还有一个,还有两个
.还有一、二、三、四
[AWFUL BAND SOUND]
[可怕的乐队声音]
.OK, new theory
.好吧，新理论
Maybe we should place
.quietly no one can hear us
也许我们应该放置
.安静地没有人能听到我们的声音
Well, maybe we wouldn't sound-
so bad if some people didn't
好吧，也许我们不会听起来——
如果有些人不这样做就太糟糕了
try to play with
.big, meaty claws
尝试玩
.大而多肉的爪子
?What did you say, punk-
？你说什么，朋克-
!Big, meaty claws-
！又大又多肉的爪子-
Well, these claws ain't-
.for just attractin' mates
好吧，这些爪子不是——
.只是为了吸引伴侣
.Bring it on, old man-
.来吧，老家伙-
!Bring it on
！来吧
.No, people-
.不，人们-
.Let's be smart and bring it off
.让我们聪明起来并实现它
Oh, so now the talking cheese-
.is going to preach to us
哦，现在会说话的奶酪——
.将向我们宣讲
!Wait, wait-
！等等，等等——
.I know
。我知道
.Tensions are high
.紧张局势很高
[CRASH]
[碰撞]
[CHATTER]
[喋喋不休]
There's a deposit on
.that equipment, people
有押金在
.设备、人员
[CHATTER]
[喋喋不休]
[SCREECHING TIRES]
.CRASH] Settle down]
[轮胎吱吱作响]
.CRASH]安定下来]
!Wait
！等待
!Ha ya-
！哈耶-
.Hey, class is over-
.嘿，下课了-
.OK, see you tomorrow-
.好的，明天见-
[CHATTER]
[喋喋不休]
.Well, you did it-
.好吧，你做到了-
You took my one
chance at happiness
你拿走了我的一个
幸福的机会
and crushed it-- crushed it into
.little, tiny, bit-sized pieces
并把它压碎——把它压碎成
.小的、微小的、有点大小的碎片
I really had expected
.better of you people
我真的预料到了
.你们中更好的人
I guess I'm a
.loser for that too
我想我是一个
.也是失败者
Don't bother
.showing up tomorrow
别打扰
.明天出现
I'll just tell them you all
.died in a marching accident
我会告诉他们一切
.在行军事故中死亡
.So thanks-- thanks for nothing
.所以谢谢——没什么感谢
.You're welcome-
。不客气-
?What kind of monsters are we-
？我们是什么样的怪物——
That poor creature came
.to us in his hour of need
那个可怜的生物来了
.在他需要的时候给我们
.And we failed him
.我们让他失望了
Squidward's always
been there for us
章鱼哥永远是
一直在我们身边
.when it was convenient for him
.当他方便的时候
Evelyn, when your
little Jimmy was
伊芙琳，当你
小吉米是
,trapped in a fire
?who rescued him
，被困在火中
?谁救了他
.A fireman-
.消防员-
And Larry, when-
your heart gave out
还有拉里，当——
你的心已经耗尽
from all those canning
?pills, who revived you
来自所有那些罐头
?药丸，是谁让你复活的
.Some guy in an ambulance-
.救护车里的某个人-
.Right-
。正确的-
So if we all could just pretend
that Squidward was a fireman
所以如果我们都能假装
章鱼哥是一名消防员
or some guy in an
ambulance, then I
或者某个人在
救护车，然后我
am sure we could all pull
together and discover what it
我确信我们都能拉
一起发现它是什么
truly means to be
.in a marching band
真正意味着是
.在军乐队中
!Yeah, for the firemen-
！是的，对于消防员来说——
!Yeah-
！是的-
Now, let's make-
.Squidward proud
现在，让我们——
.章鱼哥骄傲
.A one, a two, a skilledilly doo
.一，二，熟练地嘟
I knew this was-
.going to happen
我知道这是——
.将会发生
They're just going to have
.to find another band to play
他们只会有
.寻找另一个乐队来演奏
--I just hope that
.Squilliam doesn't find out
——我只是希望
.斯奎利亚姆没有发现
[Squilliam! [SCREAMS
?What are you doing here
[斯奎利亚姆！ [尖叫声
?你在这里做什么
I just wanted to-
.watch you blow it
我只是想——
.看你吹它
?So where's your band
？那么你的乐队在哪里
.They couldn't come-
.他们不能来-
.They died
.他们死了
?Then who's that-
？那是谁-
!Ah-
！啊-
.That would be my band
.那将是我的乐队
We're ready to-
.perform Squidward
我们准备好——
.执行章鱼哥
,Well, Squiddy-
this is exactly how
，好吧，乌贼-
正是这样
.I pictured your band would look
.我想象你的乐队会是什么样子
.That's his eager face-
.那是他热切的脸-
.Ha ha ha ha ha-
.哈哈哈哈哈哈-
I guess this'll-
be the last time
我想这会-
是最后一次
.I can show my face in this town
.我可以在这个小镇露面
.That's the spirit Squidward-
.这就是章鱼哥的精神-
.ANNOUNCER: OK, football fans
.播音员：好的，球迷们
Put your hands together for
.the Bikini Bottom Super Band
双手合十，为了
.比基尼泳裤超级带
[CHEERS]
[干杯]
Those are some-
.ugly looking fish
这些是一些——
.长相丑陋的鱼
Maybe we're near one of-
.those toxic waste dumps
也许我们正接近其中之一——
.那些有毒废物堆放场
.I think I'm going to be sick-
.我想我会生病-
OK, everybody, let's get this-
,over with-- one, two, three
好吧，大家，让我们来——
,结束--一、二、三
.four
.四
[BAND PLAYING]
[乐队演奏]
.SINGING] The winner takes all]-
.SINGING]胜者为王]-
It's the thrill
.of one more kill
这就是刺激
.再杀一次
The last one to fall will
.never sacrifice their will
最后一个倒下的人将会
.永远不要牺牲自己的意志
Don't ever look back on
.the world closing in
永远不要回头看
.世界正在逼近
The only attack on
.the wings of the wind
唯一的攻击
.风之翼
.Oh, the games will begin
.哦，比赛要开始了
,And it's sweet, sweet
.sweet victory, yeah
,而且很甜很甜
.甜蜜的胜利，是的
.And it's ours for the taking
.这是我们的了
.It's ours for the fight
.这是我们的战斗
,And it's sweet, sweet
.sweet, victory, yeah
,而且很甜很甜
.甜蜜，胜利，是的
.And the one who's last to fall
.最后一个倒下的人
.Sweet, sweet, sweet victory
.甜蜜，甜蜜，甜蜜的胜利
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐播放]